Finding Aid for Provost and Executive Vice-President for Academic Affairs (University of Michigan) Staff Files
Bentley Historical Library
- Monts, Lester P., 1974-2009; 41.85 linear feet
  - Awards
    - Harold Johnson Diversity Service Award
      - 1997/1998
        - General (Box 543)
        - Gutierrez, David (Box 543)
        - Ijsselmuiden, Carel (Box 543)
        - Islam, Lateef (Box 543)
        - Knefelkamp, L. Lee (Box 543)
        - Lapchick, Richard (Box 543)
        - Levine, Lawrence (Box 543)
        - Lopez, Ian F. Haney (Box 543)
        - Onwurah, Ngozi (Box 543)
        - Osborne, June (Box 543)
        - Pillai, Janet (Box 543)
        - Proctor, Larry (Box 543)
        - Sugrue, Thomas J. (Box 543)
        - Zaldivar, Alfredo and Rolando Estevez (Box 543)
      - 1998/1999
        - Baca, Jimmy Santiago (Box 543)
        - Coakley, Jay J. (Box 543)
        - Escalante, Jacob and Esther (Box 543)
        - Estevez, Ronando -- Anthropology (Box 543)
        - General (Box 543)
        - Laferriere, Dany -- Romance Languages (Box 543)
        - Montejano, David (Box 543)
        - Prather, Anita Singleton (Box 543)
        - Robaina, Tomas Fernandez (Box 543)
        - Visiting Professors Representatives Meetings (Box 543)
        - Williams, Betty (Box 543)
      - 1999/2000
        - Berry, Bertice (Box 543)
        - Blackman, Toni (Box 543)
        - Cliff, Michelle (Box 543)
        - Deloria, Philip (Box 543)
        - Ettawageshik, Frank (Box 543)
        - Foster, Lenny (Box 543)
        - General, 2 folders (Box 543)
        - Gomes, Flora, includes photograph (Box 543)
        - Herman, Allen (Box 543)
        - Hogan, Moses (Box 543)
        - Honkala, Cheri and Marian Kramer -- Sociology (Box 543)
        - Ignace, Chief Ron E. (Box 543)
        - Joaquin, Angelo (Box 543)
        - Mason, John (Box 543)
        - Morejon, Nancy (Box 543)
        - Nunn, Dorsey (Box 543)
        - Picot, Sandra (Box 543)
        - Reed, Adolph and Kenneth Warren (Box 543)
        - White, Joseph (Box 543)
      - 2000/2001
        - Agosin, Marjorie -- American Culture (Box 543)
        - Arnal, Jose Rafael Castillo (Box 543)
        - Bhabha, Homi, Carole Boyce Davies, and Joan Dayan (Box 543)
        - Chancy, Myriam (Box 543)
        - Fulbeck, Lawrence "Kip" -- American Culture (Box 543)
        - Final Report, 2 folders (Box 543)
        - General (Box 543)
        - Hendricks, Constance Smith -- University of South Carolina (Box 544)
        - Oboler, Suzanne -- Latinos in Popular Culture (Box 544)
        - Saunders, Shari -- Victor Lee Lewis, Peggy McIntosh, and Hugh James Vazquez -- Diversity Talks (Box 544)
        - Serote, Mongane -- South Africa (Box 544)
        - Siebers, Tobin (Box 544)
        - Simone, Nina -- UMS (Box 544)
      - 2001/2002
        - Arevalo, Roberto (Box 544)
        - Azmi, Shabana (Box 544)
        - Boal, Augusto (Box 544)
        - Dixon-Gottschild, Brenda (Box 544)
        - Edwards, Brent, Nikhil Singh, and Isaac Julien (Box 544)
        - Final Report (Box 544)
        - General (Box 544)
        - Lamming, George (Box 544)
        - Lee, Anthony (Box 544)
        - Long, Jerome and Newton (Box 544)
        - Maultsby, Paula and Susan Smith (Box 544)
        - Phillips, Janice (Box 544)
        - Public Health Lecture Series (Box 544)
        - Sizemore, Barbara (Box 544)
      - 2002/2003
        - Brown, Velvet (Box 544)
        - Bumbry, Grace (Box 544)
        - Child Advocacy Seminar -- Elizabeth Goodenough (Box 544)
        - Final Report (Box 544)
        - General (Box 544)
        - Giger, Joyce Newman (Box 544)
        - Hinds, Ruby (Box 544)
        - Lamming, George (Box 544)
        - Sphinx (Box 544)
        - Salinas, Raul (Box 544)
        - Sutton, Sharon, Roberta Uno, and Sekou Sundiata (Box 544)
      - 2003/2004
        - Arroyo, Martina (Box 544)
        - Davis, Angela (Box 544)
        - Final Report (Box 544)
        - General (Box 544)
        - Owens, Robert (Box 544)
        - Oshitola, Kolawole (Box 544)
        - Pinson, Hermine (Box 544)
        - Vargas, George (Box 544)
      - 2004/2005
        - Baez, Josefina (Box 544)
        - Blackwell, Maylei (Box 544)
        - Curtis, Christopher (Box 544)
        - General (Box 544)
        - Hammad, Suheir (Box 544)
        - Imani Winds Quartet (Box 544)
        - Macas, Luis (Box 544)
        - Osamare, Halifu (Box 544)
        - Sphinx (Box 544)
        - Strickland, Ora Lee (Box 544)
        - Thowdk, Didik Nini (Box 544)
        - Wilkerson, Margaret (Box 544)
      - 2005/2006
        - Cisneros, Sandra (Box 544)
        - Clark, Wesley (Gen.) (Box 544)
        - General (Box 544)
        - Ruiz, Vicki (Box 544)
        - Split Britches (Lois Weaver and Peggy Shaw) (Box 544)
      - 2006/2007
        - Blyden-Taylor, Brainer -- School of Music (Daniel Washington) (Box 544)
        - Coleman, Bernice (Box 544)
        - Djangrang, Nimrod Bena (Box 544)
        - Final Report (Box 544)
        - General (Box 544)
        - Kung, Lisa (Box 544)
        - Norris, Zachary (Box 544)
        - Pratt, Awadagin -- School of Music (Daniel Washington) (Box 544)
        - Smith, Christina (Box 544)
        - Sphinx Orchestra Concert (Box 544)
    - Lecturers' Professional Development Fund (LPDF)
      - 1997 (Box 544)
      - 1998 (Box 544)
      - 1999 (Box 544)
      - 1999-2000 (Box 544)
      - 2000 (Box 545)
      - 2001-2002, 2 folders (Box 545)
      - 2001-2002 (Box 545)
      - 2002-2003 (Box 545)
    - Presidential Professors
      - Cruz, Victor H., 1993-1994 (Box 545)
      - Diouf, Mamadou, 1998-1999 (Box 545)
      - General, 1995-1996 (Box 545)
      - Hill-Collins, Patricia, 1994-1995 (Box 545)
      - Long, Charles, 1998-1999 (Box 545)
      - Pantojas Garcia, Emilio, 1995 (Box 545)
      - Primus, Pearl, 1993-1994 (Box 545)
      - Reynolds, Pamela, 1999 (Box 545)
      - Zavella, Patricia, 1994 (Box 545)
    - Thurnau Professors
      - Background, 1981-2001 (Box 545)
      - General, 1989-1999 (Box 545)
      - Proposals, School of Art, 1994 (Box 545)
      - 2001/2002
        - General (Box 545)
        - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of
          - LeCuyer, Annette (Box 545)
        - Engineering, College of
          - Fogler, Scott (Box 545)
          - Grizzle, Jessy (Box 545)
          - Holloway, James (Box 545)
          - Katopodes, Nikolaos (Box 545)
          - Kaviany, Massoud (Box 545)
          - Liu, Yili (Box 545)
          - Meadows, Guy (Box 545)
          - Powell, Kenneth (Box 545)
          - Soloway, Elliot (Box 545)
        - Literature, Science and the Arts
          - Bell, Betty (Box 545)
          - Burns, Dan (Box 545)
          - Paris, Scott (Box 545)
          - Porter, Brian (Box 545)
          - Rasmussen, Paul (Box 546)
          - Sharf, Robert (Box 546)
          - Van der Pluijm, Ben (Box 546)
          - Velleman, J. David (Box 546)
        - Music, School of
          - Parmentier (Box 546)
        - Social Work, School of
          - Checkoway, Barry (Box 546)
      - 2002/2003
        - General (Box 546)
        - Business, School of
          - Cameron III, George D. (Box 546)
        - Engineering, College of
          - Folger, Scott (Box 546)
          - Grizzle, Jessy (Box 546)
          - Holloway, James (Box 546)
          - Katopodes, Nikolaos (Box 546)
          - Kaviany, Massoud (Box 546)
          - Liu, Yili (Box 546)
        - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of
          - Alexander, William "Buzz" (Box 546)
          - Bergman, Joel (Box 546)
          - Gehring, William (Box 546)
          - Hume, Richard (Box 546)
          - Markovits, Andrei (Box 546)
          - Mitani, John (Box 546)
          - Porter, Brian (Box 546)
          - Schiefelbein, John (Box 546)
          - Van der Pluijm, Ben (Box 546)
        - Medical School
          - Johnson, Timothy R.B. (Box 546)
      - 2003/2004
        - General (Box 546)
        - Business, School of
          - Moore, Scott A. (Box 546)
        - Education, School of
          - Moje, Elizabeth B. (Box 546)
        - Engineering, College of
          - Chen, Peter M. (Box 546)
          - Jones, J. Wayne (Box 546)
          - Grizzle, Jessy W. (Box 546)
          - Kaviany, Massoud (Box 546)
          - Wight, James K. (Box 546)
        - Kinesiology, Division of
          - Ulrich, Dale (Box 546)
        - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of
          - Banaszak-Holl, Mark (Box 546)
          - Colás, Santiago (Box 546)
          - Fink, William L. (Box 546)
          - Gehring, William H. (Box 546)
          - Juster, Susan (Box 546)
          - McKay, Timothy (Box 546)
          - Owen, Robert M. (Box 546)
          - Schiefelbein, John (Box 546)
          - Scodel, Ruth (Box 546)
        - Medical School
          - Carey, Thomas E. (Box 546)
        - Music, School of
          - Borders, James M. (Box 546)
          - Kibbie, James W. (Box 546)
          - Ormand, E. Fred (Box 546)
        - Natural Resources and Environment, School of (Box 547)
          - Diana, James (Box 547)
        - Pharmacy, College of
          - Smith, David E. (Box 547)
            - Pharmacokinetics Computer-Aided Learning Modules, 2000
      - 2004/2005
        - General (Box 547)
        - Nominees, 2 folders (Box 547)
      - 2005/2006
        - General (Box 547)
        - Nominees, 2 folders (Box 551)
      - 2006/2007 (Box 551)
      - 2007/2008 (Box 552)
    - Rhodes/Marshall/Mitchell Scholars
      - 1995/1996
        - General (Box 552)
      - 1997/1998
        - Reception (Box 552)
      - 1998/1999
        - General (Box 552)
        - Reception (Box 552)
      - 1999/2000
        - Nominees (Box 552)
        - Reception (Box 552)
        - 2000/2001 (Box 547)
        - General (Box 552)
        - 2001/2002 (Box 547)
        - General (Box 552)
        - 2004/2005 (Box 547)
        - Reception (Box 552)
        - Selection Process (Box 552)
        - Selections (Box 552)
      - 2005/2006
        - General (Box 547)
        - Interviews, 2006 (Box 547)
        - Marshall Scholarship Materials (Box 547)
        - Mitchell Scholarship Materials (Box 547)
        - Rhodes Scholarship Materials (Box 547)
      - 2007/2008
        - General (Box 547)
      - 2008/2009
        - General (Box 552)
        - Reception (Box 552)
      - Senior Scholarships Committee
        - 1986-1992 (Box 552)
        - 1993-1994 (Box 552)
        - 1995-1996 (Box 547)
      - Senior Scholarships Committee Lists, 1992-1998 (Box 547)
      - Senior Scholarships Events, 1993-1994 (Box 552)
      - Senior Scholarships -- Marshall, 1990-1993 (Box 552)
        [Student records restricted until July 01, 2078 ]
      - Senior Scholarships -- Recommendations
        - 1992-1994 (Box 552)
        - 1996 (Box 552)
      - Senior Scholarships -- Rhodes, 1992-1995 (Box 552)
      - Senior Scholarships -- Rhodes/Marshall, 1992-1995 (Box 552)
      - Student Applications
        - 2005
          - Barrett, Elizabeth (Box 552)
          - Bovair, Elizabeth (Box 552)
          - Chang, Andrew (Box 552)
          - DeBartolo, Jessica (Box 552)
          - Honig, Dan (Box 552)
          - Johnson, Christopher (Box 552)
          - Larson, Peter (Box 552)
          - Levine, Miriam (Box 552)
          - Moore, Madison (Box 552)
          - Murphy, Shilpa (Box 552)
          - Rohatgi, Pratik (Box 552)
          - Saunders-Scott, Molly (Box 552)
          - Torigian, Joseph (Box 552)
        - 2006
          - Becker, Matthew (Box 552)
          - Chen, Lyric (Box 552)
          - Polcyn, Lucus (Box 552)
          - Soble, Maya (Box 552)
          - Sparks, Kendal (Box 552)
        - 2007
          - Cromwell, Michael (Box 552)
          - Ketchum, Stephanie (Box 552)
          - Thang, Loc (Box 552)
          - Tuckery, Colin (Box 552)
          - Wisniewski, Tom (Box 552)
        - 2008
          - Beamer, Christine (Box 552)
          - Dedrick, Maia (Box 552)
          - El-Sayed, Abdulrahman (Box 552)
          - Espahbodi, Sam (Box 552)
          - Rao, Neil (Box 552)
          - Sparks, Kendal (Box 552)